

PROFILE

I'm Nura Alam. At present I'm a student and studying at Hajee Mohammad Danesh Science & Technology University. Besides my study I'm also working as a frontend web designer at Fiverr. I have very efficient knowledge in HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, JavaScript, React Js, Angular Js and Next Js.

I've already worked with many projects on frontend web development and built many websites for my clients.

CONTACT

PHONE: 01854405107

WEBSITE: devnuralam.com

EMAIL: nuralam.hstu.930@gmail.com

HOBBIES

Traveling Gardening Singing Discussing

NURA ALAM

Student

EDUCATION

Hajee Mohammad Danesh Science and Technology University 2017 - present

[At present I am completing bachelor degree on Electronics and Communication Engineering from this institute.]

LEDP LOT-09

July-2020 – August-2020

[I've completed a course on Web Design and Development from this institute in the last year.]

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend (React) Web Developer (Synergy Labs Team) [Frontend Design]

August-2021-present

[Here I work as a frontend web developer. This organization collects requirements from their clients and provide this work to the workers like me to do the job.]

Junior Level Frontend Web Developer (f/m/d) (Remote)

September-2021-present

[Here I work as a junior frontend web developer. In this institution about 200 junior web designer is working like me. This job is handled by their stuff remotely.]

SKILLS

